http://redmen.com/privacy-policy.html

----
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you use our site, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our site, new features and other updates.
SECTION 2 - CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at webmaster@redmen.com
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 - ECOMMERCE
We do not conduct any e-commerce on redmen.com
Payment:
If for any reason we were to collect a payment from you it would be through a trusted, third party payment processor and we would not collect any financial information from you.
SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us such as Internet data center and hosting, do not collect any information about you.
If you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our site, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 - SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
COOKIES
Our servers use cookies for standard and commonly accepted practices such as maintaining your session and identifying you for access to certain areas of our site that require an account.
SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our site is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell features to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at webmaster@redmen.com or by mail at redmen.com
[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]
ContactPrivacyTermsTwitterFacebookYouTubeLinkedInRideSharesContributeMission Statement
